(Sheldon:)Clarify something for me.
(Sheldon:)Isn't the point
(Sheldon:)of a communal meal
(Sheldon:)the exchange of ideas
and opinions?
(Sheldon:)An opportunity to consider
important issues of the day?
(Leonard:)It is.
(Leonard:)You just kind of put
a damper on things
(Leonard:)when you said,
"The next person I see talking
(Leonard:)with food in their mouth
will be put to death."
(Sheldon:)Well, we could argue about
who said what all night long,
(Sheldon:)but to set things back
on course,
(Sheldon:)I will propose
a new topic of conversation.
(Leonard:)Great.
(Sheldon:)What is the best number?
(Sheldon:)By the way, there's only
one correct answer.
5,318,008?
(Sheldon:)Wrong.
(Sheldon:)The best number is 73.
(Sheldon:)You're probably wondering why.
(Raj:)No. Uh-uh.
We're good.